const Questions = [
  {
    question: "What does the word unicorn mean ?",
    answers: ["Nice fur", "4 hooves", "Soft nose", "1 horn"],
    correct: "1 horn",
  },
  {
    question: "Fill in the blank. There____unicorns in My Little Pony",
    answers: ["Are", "Are not", "Have never been", "Are probably"],
    correct: "Are",
  },
  {
    question: "Who first wrote about unicorns ?",
    answers: ["Shakespeare", "Ancient Greeks", "Chinese Court", "Uncle Bob"],
    correct: "Chinese Court",
  },
  {
    question:
      "According to the Harry Potter books, what colour is unicorn's blood ?",
    answers: ["Blue", "Pink", "Silver", "Black"],
    correct: "Silver",
  },
  {
    question: "When was the first written record of an unicorn ?",
    answers: ["400 BC", "1400 AD", "400 AD", "666 AD"],
    correct: "400 BC",
  },
  {
    question: "What was the name of the toy unicorn in Toy Story 3 ?",
    answers: ["Trixie", "Wheezy", "Buttercup", "Peanut"],
    correct: "Buttercup",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of these is supposed to be one of an unicorn's magic powers ?",
    answers: [
      "Laser vision",
      "Healing people",
      "Teleportation",
      "Breathing fire",
    ],
    correct: "Healing people",
  },
  {
    question: "What do you call a baby unicorn ?",
    answers: ["Sparkle", "Unicornlet", "Unicornling", "Uni"],
    correct: "Sparkle",
  },
  {
    question: "Which part of the UK has an unicorn as its national animal ?",
    answers: ["England", "Wales", "Northern Ireland", "Scotland"],
    correct: "Scotland",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these go best with unicorns ?",
    answers: ["Hurricanes", "Tsunamis", "Rainbows", "Fog"],
    correct: "Rainbows",
  },
];
